point2homes.com 2019-04-01

# Point2 | Real Estate Marketing | Listing Syndication

Point2 is committed to a zero-tolerance, anti-Spamming policy. Under this policy, we prohibit Spam from being sent over the Point2 Agent network by users of Point2 Agent. 

Infringements of this policy include, but are not limited to:

  1. Sending mail to users who do not desire to receive such mail.
  2. Harassment, whether through language, frequency or size of messages, is prohibited.
  3. Email using a third party's domain name without permission.
  4. Email containing threat of personal injury or threat of property damage.
  5. Email used for any direct or perceived illegal purpose.

In the course of monitoring individuals improperly using this system, or in the course of system maintenance, the activities of users may be monitored. Anyone using Point2 Agent expressly consents to such monitoring. 

Infringements of this policy can result in the following: 

  1. A warning from Point2, via email or phone.
  2. Temporary or permanent disconnection of service.

Point2 uses cookies and similar technologies to collect information. 

Our websites, Point2.com and Point2Homes.com, use cookies to deliver content specific to your interest, to make sure you do not see the same ad repeatedly, to save your password so you don’t have to re-enter it each time you visit our site, and for the other purposes set out below: 

  * To help us recognize you and to find your account information in our database when you access a service so you do not need to log in at every visit, this helps to provide you with service tailored to your specific needs and interests 
  * To estimate our audience size, your browser is given a unique cookie that helps us determine whether yours is a repeat visit or a first visit 
  * To determine the browser the visitor uses so the site can be designed to work properly with the most common versions of different browsers 

Demographics and profile data is used to tailor our visitor’s experience at out site and display the content according to their preferences. Cookies cannot be used to read data off your hard drive, and cannot retrieve information from any other cookies created by other Web sites. We use cookies on this manner to help us understand how visitors use our site, and to help us to improve our site. Please note that advertisers that place ads on Point2.com may use cookies. 

Most internet browsers accept cookies automatically, but you can change the settings of your browser to erase cookies or prevent automatic acceptance if you prefer. You can also adjust all of your cookie settings on this site. 

By visiting our Services, you consent to the placement of cookies and beacons in your browser and HTML-based emails in accordance with this Privacy Policy. 

Point2 is committed to maintaining the accuracy, confidentiality and security of personal information. We have accepted 10 Principles established by the Canadian Standards Association's Model Code. They are as follows: 

Accountability:   
Point2 employees are responsible for maintaining and protecting personal information under their control. Point2 has designated an individual to oversee the company's compliance with the 10 principles. 

Identifying Purposes:   
We identify the purposes for which personal information is collected. 

Consent:   
We only collect, use and disclose your personal information with your knowledge and consent, except where otherwise required or permitted by law. 

Limiting Collection:   
We limit collection of your personal information to only those details that are necessary for the purposes identified. 

Limiting Use, Disclosure and Retention:   
Personal information is only used or disclosed for the purpose that it was collected, unless otherwise consented, or when required or permitted by law. We only retain your personal information for the period of time required to fulfill the purposes for which it was collected. 

Accuracy:   
We keep personal information we collect as accurate, complete and up-to-date as necessary to fulfill the purposes for which it was collected. 

Safeguards:   
We protect personal information we collect with security safeguards appropriate to the sensitivity of the information. 

Openness:   
Information about our policies and practices relating to the management of personal information is made readily available to you. 

Access:   
At your request, we inform you of the existence, use and disclosure of your personal information, and provide access to the information. You can challenge the accuracy and completeness of your information, and amend it as necessary. 

Challenging Compliance:   
You can contact us with any questions, complaints or suggestions with respect to the above principles. 

What is Personal Information?   
Personal information is broadly defined as information about an identifiable individual, but does not include the name, title, business address or telephone number of an employee of an organization. Data collected with personal identifiers removed, so that it is impossible to determine the identity of the person to whom the information relates, is not considered personal information. 

Our Relationship With You:   
We want to provide you with service on an ongoing basis and to establish a long-lasting relationship with you that will grow and change to meet your needs. With your permission, we collect personal information about you to: 

  1. Identify you
  2. Establish and maintain a relationship with you, and to provide you with better service
  3. Protect you, and us, against error and fraud
  4. Comply with legal requirements

Your personal information may also be used to create statistics about Point2's business. We will not sell your personal information to any organization, for any purpose. 

Consent:   
The cornerstone to protecting your privacy is consent. We will only collect, use and disclose your personal information with your consent, except where otherwise permitted by law. We do not, as a condition of the supply of a product or service to you, require you to consent to the collection, use or disclosure of your personal information beyond that information which is required to provide our services to you. 

You may choose not to provide us with any of your personal information. However, if you make this choice we may not be able to provide you with the product, service or information that you requested or that could be offered to you. 

Types of Consent:   
Consent can be express or it may be implied in appropriate circumstances. 

Express Consent can be given in writing, in person, electronically, by telephone or by using a check-off box. 

Implied Consent occurs when surrounding circumstances exist that lead a reasonable person to believe that this consent had been given, although no direct, express or explicit words of agreement are transmitted. 

Withdrawing Consent:   
We only collect, use and disclose your personal information with your knowledge and consent, except where otherwise required or permitted by law. 

Limiting Collection:   
You may withdraw consent at any time, subject to legal or contractual restrictions and reasonable notice. If you withdraw consent, we will inform you of the implications of such withdrawal. To withdraw consent, simply contact us and advise us of what personal information you no longer wish us to use. 

What Safeguards Do We Have in Place?   
Point2 has developed processes and procedures to keep your Personal information safe and secure. We have appropriate safeguards in place depending on the sensitivity of the information. 

Disclosure of Personal Information:   
We will only use and disclose your personal information to fulfill the purposes for which it was collected. Any exception will be with prior consent, or as may be required by law. Also, we will keep information only for as long as it is needed to fulfill the purposes for which it was collected. 

Customer Support:   
Any attempts to undermine, slander, threaten, swear at or cause harm to a Point2 support staff is strictly prohibited and is grounds for immediate termination of account and membership in Point2. 

You may access and verify your personal information and find out to whom we have disclosed it. At the time of your request, we will need specific information from you to verify your identity before we can provide you with the personal information we hold. If you identify any incorrect or outdated information requiring amendment, please contact us. We may ask you to put your request for a correction in writing. 

We are committed to maintaining the accuracy of your personal information for as long as it is being used for the purposes we have identified. To help us keep your personal information up-to-date, we encourage you to notify us of inaccuracies or corrections as often as you wish. If you identify any incorrect or outdated information requiring amendment, please contact us. We may ask you to put your request for a correction in writing. 

For more information on the Registrant Rights and Responsibilities Under the 2009 Registrar Accreditation Agreement, please [review this link](http://www.icann.org/en/registrars/registrant-rights-responsibilities-en.htm)

Yardi Systems, Inc. and its affiliated entities (“Yardi”) is committed to protecting the privacy of individuals and achieving and maintaining the trust of our clients (“Yardi Clients” or “Clients”) and other users of and visitors to Yardi websites (collectively, “Visitors”). Central to this mission is providing a robust security and privacy program that carefully considers data protection matters across the suite of products and services offered by Yardi (“Yardi Services” or “Services”), including data stored by Yardi on behalf of its Clients and their customers in connection with our Services (“Client Data”), as well as the personal data (including such data as defined by the EU General Data Protection Regulation) provided by Clients and Visitors who visit [www.Yardi.com](http://www.yardi.com/), associated Yardi microsites and any other Yardi-controlled websites that link to this Privacy Statement (collectively, the “Yardi Sites”). 

Web Sites Covered   
This Privacy Statement describes our privacy practices regarding information we collect from individuals (“you” or “your”) who visit the Yardi Sites. When we collect personal data on the Yardi Sites, certain additional disclosures, that are specific to the context of our collection and use of the information being collected (e.g. an event or seminar registration page), may be provided to you. For the avoidance of any doubt, we will adhere to those commitments and any such additional privacy policy statements are hereby incorporated into this Privacy Statement. 

IMPORTANT: THIS PRIVACY STATEMENT DOES NOT APPLY TO CLIENT DATA   
Yardi’s confidentiality/privacy and other obligations with respect to its Services, and Client Data (as defined in the agreements for those Services), are governed solely by the agreements under which the Services are provided to our Clients. The traditional licensees of Yardi Services are residential and commercial real estate property owners and property managers (again, collectively, as used in this Privacy Statement, “Yardi Clients” or “Clients”). The other actors in the real estate economy are, of course, the residents, tenants and providers of various services for, or at, the buildings Yardi Clients own and manage. Yardi Services (by means of example only, the Yardi Voyager web-based, fully integrated end-to-end platform product suite) help our Clients manage their real estate and other assets by, among other things, facilitating communication and transactions between Yardi Clients and their tenants and service providers. Yardi generally has no direct relationship with the individuals to whom our Clients’ Client Data may pertain; Yardi merely hosts or processes such data on behalf of our Clients. Any uses of Client Data by Yardi are done so pursuant to the subscription agreement in place between Yardi and the relevant Yardi Client, or Yardi’s applicable Terms of Service, which exclusively govern Yardi’s treatment of Client Data. This Privacy Statement does not apply to Yardi Services or Client Data. If you have any questions about the data practices of a Yardi Client, using Yardi Services to process your personal information, you need to contact the Yardi Client directly, and ask for their Privacy Policy or Privacy Statement. In other words, Yardi is a data processor and not a data controller with respect to Client Data. Yardi Clients make all decisions about how or why Client Data, containing personal information or not, is to be processed, including any disclosure or transmission to third parties. If personal information pertaining to you as an individual has been submitted or entered into a Yardi Service by or on behalf of a Yardi Client, or was otherwise collected by a Yardi Service on behalf of a Yardi Client, and you wish to exercise any rights you may have to access, correct, amend or delete such Client Data, please inquire with the Yardi Client directly. If an authorized Yardi Client requests that we update or remove the data in question and the Client has no ability to do so via use of the Services, we will acknowledge their request within 30 days. 

Web Sites Not Covered   
Some Yardi Services enable Yardi Clients to create websites and applications that run natively on the Yardi platform. One such example are RENTCafé resident portals, which facilitate communication and transactions between Yardi Clients and their potential or actual tenants. Such websites are controlled by Yardi Clients, and as described above, any information submitted to or collected by such websites is Client Data to which this Privacy Statement does not apply. The terms of service and privacy policy of the third party Yardi Client governs such websites. 

Yardi is committed to promoting privacy principles and providing as much information to individuals as legally and contractually possible about the processing of their personal data. In that light, some Yardi Client-controlled websites that are created and maintained by Yardi Services may include privacy statements directly from Yardi to the users of such websites. Yardi is committed to adhering to such privacy statements. We provide these statements, or disclosures to identify Yardi as the data processor/technology platform, to disclose Yardi’s privacy practices with respect to such Client Data, and to inform the user to seek information about the privacy practices governing the website directly from the corresponding Yardi Client. To be clear, Yardi’s privacy statements on such Yardi Client controlled websites are applicable only to Yardi, and not the Yardi Client. In such privacy statements, Yardi discloses how Yardi uses and processes the information collected by and submitted to the website controlled by the Yardi Client. For the avoidance of any doubt, if you submitted personal data to a Yardi Client-controlled website created and maintained by Yardi Services (e.g. RENTCafé resident portals) and you wish to exercise any rights you may have to access, correct, amend or delete such Client Data, please inquire with the Yardi Client directly. 

Some Yardi Sites may be created and managed by Yardi Clients. Most of these websites are not accessible via the public internet. Regardless, please know that this Privacy Statement is not applicable to those websites, which are instead governed by the privacy statement of the Yardi Client that creates and manages the website. In addition, the Yardi Sites may contain links to other third-party websites. The information practices or content of such other websites is governed by the privacy statements of such other websites. Yardi encourages you to review the privacy statements of such other websites to understand their information practices. 

Information We Collect

Personally Identifiable Information. Yardi collects personally identifiable information on this Site only if you provide it. This may include, but not be limited to: the process of registering to attend an event, applying for employment with Yardi or by contacting Yardi for some other reason through a web form. In these cases only, we will require you to provide information necessary to fulfill your request, such as your name and email address. 

Generic User Information. As you navigate the Yardi Sites, Yardi may also collect generic user information through the use of commonly-used information-gathering tools, such as cookies and Web beacons. This information includes standard information from your Web browser (e.g. browser type and browser language), your Internet Protocol (“IP”) address, the URL of the page that referred you and the actions you take on the Yardi Sites (e.g. the web pages viewed, the survey responses you submit, the links clicked, etc.). 

How We Use Information We Collect   
Yardi uses the information you submit on the Yardi Sites solely to perform the services or activity being requested and to present its content to you. However, personal data will never be sold or rented. We may use third parties to perform services related to the services or activity requested, such as payment processing for any applicable fees associated with an event or transaction. These third parties have access to the information you submit only to perform these tasks on our behalf. Generic user information is referenced only to help us improve the usability of the Yardi Sites. You may be able to restrict the use of cookies by adjusting your browser’s privacy options. 

Yardi, like all organizations, is a data controller of its employees’ personal data that is processed as part of its human resources operations. If you are a Visitor located in the European Economic Area, Yardi Systems, B.V., is the data controller for any personal data collected on the Yardi Sites. For additional information about Yardi’s privacy practices relating to applying for a job at Yardi, please visit our [Yardi Careers Privacy Policy](https://careers.yardi.com/privacy-policy/) (which is hereby incorporated by reference). 

Our legal basis for collecting and using the information and personal data described in this Privacy Statement will depend on the information or personal data concerned and the specific context in which we collect it. However, we will normally collect personal data from you only where we have your consent to do so, where we need the personal data to perform a contract with you, or where the processing is in our legitimate interests and not overridden by your data protection interests or fundamental rights and freedoms. In some cases, we may also have a legal obligation to collect personal data from you. 

Public Forums and Customer Testimonials   
Yardi may provide bulletin boards, blogs or chat rooms on Yardi Sites. Any information or personal information you choose to submit in such a forum may be read, collected or used by others who visit these forums, and may be used to send you unsolicited messages. Yardi is not responsible for any information or personal data you choose to submit in these public forums. 

Yardi may post a list of clients and testimonials on Yardi Sites that contain information such as client names and titles. Yardi obtains the consent of each such person prior to posting any information on such a list or posting testimonials. 

Information We Share

Service Providers

As described above, Yardi may share your personal data with contracted service providers so that these service providers can provide services on our behalf. Yardi does not share, sell, rent or trade any personal data to or with third parties for their promotional or marketing purposes. 

Yardi Affiliates

Yardi may share your personal data with affiliates of Yardi for the purpose of any necessary collaboration. For example, Yardi may need to share your information with an affiliate for job application and employment purposes. 

Yardi Successor

Yardi may share your personal data with a buyer or other successor in the event of a merger, divestiture, restructuring, reorganization, dissolution or other sale or transfer of some or all of Yardi’s assets, whether as a going concern or as part of bankruptcy, liquidation or similar proceeding, in which personal data held by Yardi about our Visitors is among the assets transferred. 

Compelled Disclosure

Yardi reserves the right to use or disclose information and personal data provided on the Yardi Sites if required by law or if Yardi reasonably believes that such use or disclosure is necessary to protect Yardi’s rights and/or to comply with a judicial proceeding, court order or legal process. 

International Transfer of Information

To facilitate Yardi’s global operations, Yardi may store, transfer and access the information and personal data you submit on the Yardi Sites around the world, including the United States, Canada and other countries in which Yardi has operations. This Privacy Statement shall apply even if Yardi transfers such information or personal data to other countries. By registering to attend an event, contacting us through our web form or providing information or personal data to us on any Yardi Sites in any other context, you consent to the transfer of your information and personal data among these facilities, including those located outside your home country. 

If you are located in the European Economic Area (“EEA”), we will comply with applicable legal requirements providing adequate protection for the transfer of personal data to recipients in countries outside of the EEA. In all such cases, we will only transfer your personal data if: 

The country to which the personal data will be transferred has been granted a European Commission adequacy decision;   
The recipient of the personal data is located in the U.S. and has certified to the EU-U.S. Privacy Shield Framework; or 

We have put in place appropriate safeguards with respect to the transfer, for example the EU Model Clauses. 

You may request a copy of the safeguards that we have put in place in respect of transfers of personal data by contacting us as described in the How to Contact Us section below. 

Communications Preferences

Yardi offers Visitors who provide contact information a means to choose how Yardi uses the information provided. You may manage your receipt of marketing and non-transactional communications by clicking on the “unsubscribe” link located on the bottom of Yardi’s marketing emails. Additionally, you may specify your communications preferences using our Privacy Feedback form. Yardi Clients cannot opt out of receiving transactional emails related to their account with Yardi or the Services. 

Your California Privacy Rights

As already stated elsewhere in this Privacy Statement, and in accordance with California Civil Code Section § 1798.83, please know that Yardi does not disclose personal data collected on the Yardi Sites to third parties for their direct marketing purposes. (California Civil Code Section § 1798.83 permits users of a website that are California residents to request certain information regarding the disclosure of personal data to third parties for their direct marketing purposes). 

Children Under the Age of 16

Yardi Sites are not intended for children under 16 years of age. No one under age 16 may provide any information to, or on, any Yardi Sites. We do not knowingly collect personal data from children under 16. If you are under 16, do not use any Yardi Sites, and do not provide any information via any Yardi Sites. If we learn we have collected or received personal data from a child under 16 without verification of parental consent, we will delete that data. If you believe any Yardi Sites may have collected personal data from or about a child under 16, please contact our Legal Department at (800) 866-1124. 

Rights of Individuals

Visitors who wish to correct, update, change, or erase the personal data they submit on any Yardi Sites should be able to go back to the applicable registration page or web form to edit their user or organization record. However, some of the information voluntarily submitted that is not personal data, such as a response to a poll or a survey, is typically aggregated and thus not correctable, updatable, changeable, or erasable. For additional information or problems accessing your information from such page, call us at (800) 866-1124, or contact us using our [Privacy Feedback](https://www.yardi.com/about-us/privacy-statement/privacy-statement-feedback/) form. 

If you consider that we have processed your personal data in violation of applicable law and failed to remedy such violation to your reasonable satisfaction, you may also lodge a complaint with the data protection supervisory authority in your country. 

Data Retention

Yardi retains the personal data we receive on the Yardi Sites for the duration of your relationship with Yardi, plus a reasonable period thereafter as necessary to fulfil the purposes described above. Retention periods may be extended if we are required to preserve your personal data because of litigation, investigations and other similar proceedings, or if a longer retention period is required or permitted by applicable law. 

Security

Yardi is committed to protecting the security of any personal data you provide to us. Yardi uses appropriate administrative, technical, and physical security measures to protect any such information you submit. Despite these protections, no one, including Yardi, can guarantee the security of any data submitted over the Internet. 

Copyright Policy

Reporting Copyright Infringement Claims

Yardi respects the intellectual property of others, and we ask our users, property managers, owners, and commercial brokers to do the same. Yardi has implemented procedures for receiving written notification of claimed infringements and for processing such claims in accordance with the Digital Millennium Copyright Act, 17 U.S.C. Section 512 (“DMCA”). 

If a third party believes that its work has been copied in a way that constitutes copyright infringement, or its intellectual property rights have been otherwise violated, it should provide the designated agent with the following information: (i) an electronic or physical signature of the person authorized to act on behalf of the owner of the copyright or other intellectual property interest; (ii) a description of the copyrighted work or other intellectual property that it claims has been infringed; (iii) a description of where the material that it claims is infringing is located on the Yardi Site; (iv) its address, telephone number, and email address; (v) a statement that it has a good faith belief that the disputed use is not authorized by the copyright owner, its agent, or the law; and (vi) a statement made under penalty of perjury, that the above information in your notice is accurate and that it is the copyright or intellectual property owner or authorized to act on the copyright or intellectual property owner’s behalf. 

DMCA Notices should be sent to our designated copyright agent: Jocelyn.Belloni@Yardi.com or via mail Attn: DMCA Agent – Legal Department, Yardi Systems, Inc., 430 S. Fairview Avenue, Santa Barbara CA 93117. 

Repeat Infringers

It is Yardi’s policy, in appropriate circumstances, to terminate the accounts of parties who are repeat infringers or are repeatedly charged with infringement. 

Changes to this Privacy Statement

Yardi reserves the right to change this Privacy Statement from time to time. Your continued use of any Yardi Sites after we make changes is deemed to be acceptance of those changes, so please check this Privacy Statement periodically for updates. 

Contacting Us

If you have any questions about this Privacy Statement, or you would like to exercise any of your rights, please let us know by contacting us using any of the methods below: 

By phone at: +1 (800) 866-1124   
By email at: [privacy@yardi.com](mailto:privacy@yardi.com)   
In writing at: Attention – Privacy Manager, 430 S. Fairview, Santa Barbara, CA 93117, USA 

Last Updated: March 5, 2019
